giggle.com 2014-04-18

# Privacy & Security

giggle, Inc. considers the privacy and security of user information an integral component of the services offered at our website, giggle.com ( **Site** ). The following information explains how giggle collects and uses information obtained from users in connection with services available at the Site (taken together, the **Service** ).

## What this Policy Covers.

This Privacy Policy covers giggle’s treatment of personal information that giggle gathers when you are on the giggle website and when you use giggle services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that giggle does not own or control, or to individuals that giggle does not employ or manage.

## Personal Information Collected and How We Use It.

In order to provide you with a friendly, customized, and efficient experience, we collect personal information of several types from our customers. Please note that our site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. 

_Information You Provide to Us:_

We receive and store any information you enter on the Site or provide to us in any other way. You may be asked to provide us information about you when you create an account or registry, write a review or comment, ask a question, register to receive giggle emails, participate in contests, sweepstakes or promotions or make a product purchase. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of the features of our Site.

giggle uses the information you provide to us in order to improve the quality of the Site and Services, in certain instances, provide you with customized content according to your preferences, fulfill your requests for giggle’s products or services, and send you information about giggle and its products and services.

From time to time we might establish a business relationship or partnership with other persons or entities that we believe trustworthy and can provide additional benefits or services to our customers. We call these parties the giggle Partners. We may email you with offers from giggle Partners or, we might share and cross-reference information, including personal information about you that will enable such parties to contact you regarding products or services that may be of interest to you. _**If you do not want your personal information shared with other organizations, please contact us at 1.800.495.8577.**_

To provide you with the best possible information and service, we may combine information you give us online with information from our stores. We may also combine information with publicly available information we obtain. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you and for other promotional purposes.

At your election you may choose to stop receiving future electronic communications from giggle and/or giggle Partners by:

  * Clicking on the "unsubscribe" link and follow the instructions on how to unsubscribe included in each edition of our giggle emails;
  * changing your preferences on your account information at [http://www.giggle.com](https://www.giggle.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-giggle-Site/default/Account-Show);
  * emailing giggle Customer Service at [customerservice@giggle.com](mailto:customerservice@giggle.com) with specific instructions for the changes you wish to make; or
  * calling our Customer Service Department at 1.800-495.8577.

At your election you may choose to stop receiving future mailed communications, including catalogs, event announcements or other offers from giggle and/or our partners by calling our Customer Service Department at 1-800-495-8577.

Please note that any requests to remove or change your information or preferences may take up to forty-five days to take effect.

Cookies and Other Technology. Like many sites, our Site employs cookies and web beacons to speed your navigation of the Site, recognize you and your access privileges, and track your Site usage.

(a) Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk to enable saving of your Site preferences, and other record-keeping purposes. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. We do not combine personal information you provide to us with information collected through cookies. Most web browsers can be set to refuse cookies, although this may cause certain features of our Site or Service to cease functioning properly. The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. Please note, however, that if do not cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of some of our attractive features.

(b) Web beacons assist in delivering cookies and help us determine whether a web page on this Site has been viewed and, if so, how many times. For example, any electronic image on this Site, such as an ad banner, can function as a web beacon.

(c) We may use certain third-party companies to help us tailor site content to users. These companies may employ cookies and web beacons to help us deliver an optimized user experience on the Site. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and web beacons is not linked to any personal information collected by us. These companies are usually prohibited by contract from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than giggle. For example, when you submit a "product review" to the Site, your information will be received and managed by an independent contractor that organizes the reviews and manages that element of our Site. Before you submit a review, you should review the "Terms of Use" and "Standards for Reviews" that are linked on our Site so that you can understand the terms and conditions for acceptance and use of your information.

(d) Log Files. When you visit the Site, web servers collect information "traffic data" (such as, for example, time and date, the address of the website from which you entered the Site) about your visit, which is stored as anonymous, aggregate data. Collecting such data may entail the use of IP addresses or other numeric codes used to identify a computer. giggle uses "traffic data" to help diagnose problems with its server, analyze trends and administer the Site. Your IP address is not linked to personally identifiable information, but is used to gather broad demographic data and to monitor statistics to improve the Service. giggle may also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with its server. IP addresses are also used to provide an audit trail in the case of any attempted illegal or unauthorized use of the Site.

Product Reviews. You may choose to submit a product review. If you wish to post a review, we will ask you to login with your username and password (or if it is your first review, to create a username and password) and for your email address and zip code. When you submit a review, your geographic location will be visible to other users (your email address will be kept private). Also, any personally identifiable information that you submit as part of the review can be read or used by other visitors to the Site. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you choose to submit as part of your review. We strongly encourage you not to post or share any personally identifiable information such as your email address, phone number or address as it may pose safety concerns or otherwise violate our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.giggle.com/Terms-Conditions/terms-and-conditions,default,pg.html).

## Sharing of Information.

We may share your personal information with other individuals or non-affiliated companies in the following circumstances:

_Protection of giggle and Others:_ giggle may disclose personally identifiable data if it is required to do so by law or if the giggle has a good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to applicable laws or comply with any legal, regulatory or similar requirement or investigation, to protect or defend the rights or property of giggle or another user or to enforce the Terms of Use. 

_Business Transfers:_ giggle may transfer personally identifiable information to any successor to all or substantially all of its business or assets that concern the Service. 

_Business Partners:_ giggle may share aggregated usage and demographic information collected via our Site and Services. We may also on occasion share a portion of our postal mailing list with other reputable organizations not owned or affiliated with giggle who want to market products or services to you. If you do not want your name and address shared with other organizations or you no longer wish to receive such information from giggle, please contact our customer service department at 1-800-495-8577. 

_Agents:_ We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. 

_Contests and Promotions:_ We publicly disclose the name, city, and state of our contest and sweepstakes winners.

## Security.

Our Site incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, including Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") for all financial transactions we process. We use SSL encryption to protect your personal information online. Information collected by giggle is stored in secure operating environments that are not made generally available to the public. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, giggle cannot ensure the security of any information you provide, and you do so at your own risk. Once giggle receives your transmission, we will make reasonable efforts and comply with industry practices to ensure its security on its systems.

## Your California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties for direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: giggle Customer Relations, 158 West 27th Street, 8th Floor, New York, New York 10001. Please allow thirty days for a response.

## Updating Your Information.

giggle allows you to access the following information about you for the singular purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. You may access your account with our Site [here](https://www.giggle.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-giggle-Site/default/Account-Show).

## Third Party Sites.

The Service may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Site. These other websites are not under giggle’s control. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the Site are not covered by this Privacy Statement, and giggle is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.

## Offline Collection, Use & Disclosure of Information.

The majority of information that we collect is obtained through our Site, and this Privacy Policy applies only to that online collection of personal information. We also collect information offline, where we also try to protect the privacy of your personal information. The primary collection of offline information is done through our stores during a product purchase or a registry creation. During this collection we will ask the customer if they would like to be added to the giggle email list and/or have their information shared with our giggle Partners. Another example of offline collection of information involves someone calling us to place an order or to ask questions. When someone calls, we will ask only for the personal information we need in order to place the order or to answer the question. When we need to store information (such as order information), we will enter it into our database through SSL encryption. Another example involves faxes. If you fax something to us, we will act upon the fax and then either store it with our customer records or we will shred the fax if there is no need to retain the information. There are other ways we could learn of personal information offline (for example, we suppose someone could send us a letter including some return address information), and this Policy doesn't discuss or try to predict all of those methods or uses. We make every effort to treat offline collection, uses, and disclosures consistently with our relevant online practices.

## Changes.

giggle reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Statement at any time by posting a notice at the Site. Information collected by the Service is subject to the Privacy Statement in effect at the time of use. Last updated May 18, 2009.

## Additional Topics of Interest.

In addition to our Privacy Policy, read our Site’s [Terms and Conditions](https://www.giggle.com/Terms-Conditions/terms-and-conditions,default,pg.html).

## Contact.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Statement or your dealings at this Site, please contact giggle at:

**giggle  
Attn: Privacy Statement  
158 West 27th St, 8th Floor  
New York, New York 10001
